https://www.febc.org/privacy-policy-2/

Search
FEBC is committed to protecting your personal privacy, both online and offline. FEBC will not sell, share or trade our donors’ names or personal information with any third party. While you can use many features of our site anonymously, you are required to provide personal information when you make a donation or request mailed information or material.
How we collect and use personal information
If you respond to an offer, we must ask for your postal address so we can deliver the requested materials. We will not share your information obtained on this Web site with any third party organizations.
What we provide to third parties
FEBC does not provide any third-party access to your personal information except to facilitate your own attempts to request materials from our partner organizations in other countries.
Obtaining your consent
By using our Web site, you give FEBC permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. All e-mail that we send you has the provision to unsubscribe built-in so that you can change your mind about what we send you at any time. If you wish to verify and/or change any information that we are holding about you please call us at 1.800.523.3480 or e-mail us at info@febc.org.
If you are under the age of 18, you must not provide your name, e-mail address, or any other identifying information without the consent of your parent or guardian, or as otherwise provided for by applicable law.
Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Tell us what you think
FEBC welcomes your questions and comments about our privacy policy. Please send e-mail to info@febc.org.
Type and Press “enter” to Search
